Per usual, per usual, people, liberals more than likely, take something that is useful and turn it into useless.
The concept of two things can be true at once does not undermine the fact that even if they're both true, they're not both of equal relevance or priority.
And sometimes two things are not true.
I don't know why this white man is in here pretending to be a black woman.
Watching white men be bots who don't understand AAVE is also like its own version of fascinating.
Someone who just came in here, their name was ghetto ass bitch who stole your wig with a black woman face.
And they literally started by saying, girl, you not dragging Noah and sit your ass down because they don't understand the use of dragging two things can be true at once.
Because they're a bot pretending to be a black woman and not understanding how to use AAVE.
So they thought by saying that to me that they was in on, in on it.
No, you are not.
Y'all, I need this whole, because let me tell you something.
Nuance and two things can be true is only useful if it helps to further explain something.
However, when y'all use two things can be true to remove accountability, it refuses.
It, it, it, it, no, it, no, Danby, you didn't.
When you, oh my God.
When you all use two things can be true to avoid accountability, it literally defeats its purpose.
It defeats, it defeats its purpose.
So I'm going to say it again.
When you all use two things can be true at once.
When you all use nuance as a way to avoid accountability, as a way to avoid reality, it is not useful.
It becomes a tool of the oppressed.
It be, I mean, a tool of the oppressor.
It becomes a way to avoid actual change.
It becomes the walking of the line that they want you to do so that you don't choose a side that is of resistance.
And that's literally what it is.
It makes you a neutral ass biash.
So when I say that these women who are in position as Pam Bondi and Christine Noem and the rest of these hoes have been in position and someone says, well, yeah, but two things can be true at once.
Yes, they chose to be in position, but they're also being set up to fall.
That's an irrelevant nuance.
That's an irrelevant nuance because the choice to be in position completely makes the whether you've been set up or not irrelevant.
And for the record, the concept of being set up means that you are unaware.
That's the whole thing about being set up.
You're unaware.
You're tricked.
It's trickery.
That's what being set up is.
People are in my comments right now talking about, yeah, but they are being set up by these men.
And I just want to consistently remind you all that you cannot put the onus on where we are on gender or on race, because at the end of the day, people of all races and all gender are being complicit.
They're being complicit.
So, yes, there may be people at the top waving the wand, but there are many people who are like, yeah, keep on waving it, keep on waving it, keep on waving it.
So, when you look at that post that I just posted, you're going to see that.
Someone is saying, but if it's not a trap, what is it?
What are you talking about?
Why is it a trap?
They're all on the same side.
Is it why if it's not a trap, what is it?
It's a plan.
Plan.
And what a plan is and make a choice.
Document.
And it's been going down.
White women were choosing to sew KKK costumes.
So, I just really needed to cut it out.
And let me just add what I was talking about with the Me Too.
These women hijacked a movement that was about women who had been absolutely taken advantage of and not simply coerced, but by force.
By force were taken advantage of.
They had been drugged.
In some ways, in some cases, they had been pimped.
In some cases, they had been forcibly taken advantage of.
And that being diluted by women who simply were just like, this is uncomfortable and I may lose my job is really disconcerting to me.
As someone who has been sexually assaulted, I take great offense to that.
Y'all love Hillary Clinton after she made the concerted effort to vilify a young intern who her 60-something-year-old president husband took advantage of and ruined her life.
And y'all still call Hillary Clinton a feminist girl boss.
Y'all love to herald Hillary Clinton as this queen of the queens.
No, that woman was taken advantage of.
Did she have a choice?
Yes.
She was also operating under the white woman nonsense.
However, at the end of the day, and this is the two things can be true.
It is far more important and it is far more relevant that the president of the United States made the choice to take advantage of his position.
That is more relevant.
Listen, Hillary eating babies like this.
Nom, nom, nom, nom, nom.
I don't think y'all are really willing to understand how much people are willing to do to be famous or to have power.
I don't.
Y'all really do not really believe that.
Which is bizarre to me because you work with people and you have people in your family who you know have done more for less.
You've seen it.
You have friends who you know have been willing to do more for less.
And yet you find it shocking to imagine that somebody would do terrible things for access.
And let me also add that most of these people you do not see at all unless they want you to.
You don't see their houses.
You don't see their lives.
You don't see their friends.
You don't see their family.
You don't see nothing unless it is curated.
And you still feel like you know them and you love them because of what they put in their art.
And the fact of the matter is many things can exist.
People are multi-layered.
And for what it's worth, I want you to hear this.
For a lot of people, their art is the only place purity lives.
That is the only place that their soul speaks pure.
The rest of their lives are spent in the shitstorm of this world.
That's how you get Marvin Gaye.
That's how you get Miles Davis.
That's how you get.
We love Whitney Houston.
But, I mean, she was tormented.
Her art was the only place she could really live.
She was tormented.
Outside of it.
A lot of your favorite artists do not know what to do with that torment.
Their art is the only place where they get to really live pure.
And you're worshiping them.
You're thinking that their art is somehow a full representation of how they exist in the world.
And it is not.
And it makes you actually not even investigate how they exist in the world.
Lady Gaga, I love the music.
Terrible person.
You're as I-O.
Beyonce.
Ever.
Music for the time.
I'm not even saying they have to be out here protesting.
They're not even making music for the time.
Of an entire downfall of, um, sorry, of an uprising of American nationalism.
And Beyonce chose that as a time to do Cowboy Carter.
And y'all really fell for it.
Like, she's heralding black cowboys.
What the fuck are y'all talking about?
Leaving Kendrick out of it.
He pulled one on Drake.
But we are in a real time.
Where are they at?
They're at the Grammys.
They're in the Casita.
So shout out to all the artists who are really, like, locked in and tapped in.
And feeling the call of this moment.
And feeling the call of this awakening and of this time.
And, and, and, and leaning into it with not only their artistry, but also the rest of their soul.
Because that's really what has to happen now.
It can't be just your art.
I'm just, I'm done with it.
I heard a record from Yasuke.
Called, um,
Half Raised Flags.
Woo!
Yes, brother.
Like, I'm just, like, at some point we have to, like, we got to put our foot down.
And this two things can be true thing has got to stop.
Y'all taking it too far per usual.
The same way you've taken Joy's resistance too far per usual.
The, I mean, I ain't never seen folks dilute something like the United Statesians.
God damn.
Y'all will take some shit and run it into the ground so quick and make it damn near irrelevant.
What do you need me to tell you about Michael Jackson?
I have never thought Michael Jackson was guilty.
Either did the jury.
And guess what?
He's not.
Ba-dum-bum!
Even though they're terrified, they're to artists they can't be terrified to.
Terrified of what?
What do we, what, what does that have to do with anything?
You ain't never said a lie, Nathan.
All right, well.
I don't care about Valentine's Day.
That's why they haven't said it to me.
How do I think we as a community can stop enabling abusers and predators?
I think we can stop blaming the victims who bring them to light.
And I think we can actually publicly shame them and hurt them if necessary.
We should be stoning these people at the barbecue.
Why are we inviting folks to places who we know are harmful?
And why are we still inviting the people who are inviting folks?
This whole family dynamic nonsense, I don't get down with that either.
Well, they're family.
Fuck you and fuck them.
I'm not coming to y'all barbecue.
I was in a restaurant with my uncle recently in Grenada.
I don't even think he knew I was there, but I knew he was there.
Guess who didn't say shit?
You're really not going to go say hi?
No, fuck him.
And no, he's not a sexual abuser, but he is an emotional abuser.
When you all say I should run for president, I just need y'all to know it's literally one of the most ignorant statements you can make.
I'm a literal person.
So when you say it, I take it literally.
But I want you to understand that the context of president as it relates to the United States is literally the highest seat of imperialism, the highest visible seat of imperialism.
So you're literally saying you should attempt to be at the highest visible seat of imperialist puppetry.
When I was in third grade, I wanted to be the first black female president of the United States of America.
I am now 44 years old, and I am glad that now in my maturation and my knowledge, I understand why that is the fantastical thinking of a child.
In the 2026 of the old gods and the new, we should know better than to consider the position of the president as anything laudable or anything that anyone should actually want who has a value system.
We shouldn't have a president at all.
Negus the king is really getting y'all together, and I appreciate it.
U.S. celebrities support the Democrats because they are paid to do so.
Like, to me, this is a dumb question.
What should we do to address artists' lack of involvement and how to hold them accountable?
Why do you need my suggestion and what to do about that?
Is it just you want me to engage with you?
Because that's really obvious.
I don't have the energy for obvious anymore with y'all.
That's obvious.
Candice, get the fuck out of my chat with leaving Neverland.
The album is coming along well.
I'm working on it.
Just finding my way through, learning different skills and whatnot.
If I came with a warning label, what would it say?
100% pure and authentic.
Thank you, Lena.
I painted them.
No persona.
I stopped doing stand-up.
No love, Mikia.
Thank you, Nicole.
N-
Nicole?
Yeah.
Thank you, Nicole.
Good day, mate.
No, no one's cooking for me.
I bought something for dinner yesterday, and it has lasted for three meals.
That is a single woman who doesn't want to cook's greatest dream.
It was dinner last night.
It was lunch today.
And it was dinner tonight.
No, I don't sell my art right now.
So, anywho, I love when my cats play with the toys I got them.
I just, I feel like, I feel like such a winner.
That not having to clean up.
So, like, my cat has this little thing with the ball.
And so, he's doing this thing right now where he'll, like, run by it and be like,
and then he'll run back.
He did it three times.
If I could pick a theme song for my life, what would it be?
Denise Williams, Free.
No, I take that back.
It would be, um, Earth, Wind & Fire, Forever Wonderful.
Be ever wonderful.
Say the time is right for you tonight.
Ooh, ooh, ooh.
Not that note.
That note wasn't right.
Find your place in the something light.
Stay as you are.
All right, all right.
I don't know.
For some reason, I don't have the words in my head.
And I sing this song all the time.
Please do not come for Val knows at all.
She will dismember you verbally.
So, don't even do that.
Gonna find a few.
And what I'd like to tell you may not be as you see.
Everything today, what I want to say is be ever wonderful in your sweet way.
And at the end, he's like, don't let the world change your mind, change your mind, change
your mind.
Wine.
I don't drink.
This is limeade.
I let drinking go a long time ago.
Ain't that real Lenape?
Like, shout out to the Lenape.
You want to see the cats?
They're playing.
That's my rant for this evening.
And I, for those of y'all who are just now getting here, I will review.
Two things can be true at one time.
Should not be used to avoid accountability.
Nuance should not be used to avoid accountability.
The last video I posted was a video about how white women be trying to avoid, excuse me,
white women be trying to avoid the choices that white women are making to be in places
of power and make it about, oh, white men put them in that place to take the fall.
Completely irrelevant.
They weren't put there.
They were given the option to go there and they went.
They went.
So, making this grand statement of, well, two things can be true at once is not only irrelevant,
it's annoying.
It's annoying and it is a what about-ism that deflects from the, again, point that is being made,
which is that white women on a regular basis will choose their own personal advancement
over the decision that is best for the people.
Period.
Have a good night.